(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: For Visitors
ローソンへお越しの皆さん
Everyone visiting Lawson,
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
Lawson Campaign decided!
今回はこの6人が登場！
These 6 members appear this time!
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
Details scheduled for release on 3/9 (Mon)!
EXPOのバンダイブースも開催！
The Bandai booth at the EXPO is also open!
注目の新商品を初公開
Revealing much-anticipated new products for the first time
会場限定、スペシャルフォトブース
Venue-exclusive special photo booth
ブースで限定カードがもらえる
Get limited cards at the booth
最新プロジェクトも公開
Latest projects also revealed
会場で待ってるよ！
We're waiting for you at the venue!
Ridin' on Dreams JOYSOUND みるハコで配信決定！！
Ridin' on Dreams distribution decided on JOYSOUND Miru-Haco!!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because of you
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, thank you again and again
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's get on board!
ridin’ on dreams, yeah!
Ridin' on dreams, yeah!
woah, oh-oh, woah, oh-oh
hey! (hey!) hey! (hey!) yeah!
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
It's like I can't imagine
思いになった
It's become a feeling
ドキドキが止まらない！
I can't stop being excited!
何度迷っても...
No matter how many times we get lost...
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: For Visitors
PENLIGHT COLORS
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration now open!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because of you
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, thank you again and again
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's get on board!
Ridin' on dreams, yeah!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because of you
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, thank you again and again
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's get on board!
Ridin' on dreams, yeah!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over again
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！Ridin' on Dreams
Let's get on board! Ridin' on Dreams
Yeah！！ Wow oh oh…
Yeah!! Wow oh oh...
Hey！！ (Hey！！)
Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah！！
Yeah!!
あぁ 小さな夢から 想像できないような
Ah, from a small dream, it became a feeling...
想いになったんだ わくわく止まらない！
...I couldn't have imagined. I'm so excited!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost
絆が舵になる
Our bond becomes the rudder
ちょっとくらい怖くても大丈夫
Even if it's a little scary, it's okay
Hey！！ (Hey！！)
Hey!! (Hey!!)
(Yo-Ho!)
(Hi Hi Hi Hi)
宝鐘海賊団「出航〜!」
Houshou Pirates 'Set sail~!'
(Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!)
踊るAhoy!に見るAhoy!(ホイホーイ)
Dance Ahoy! Watch Ahoy! (Hoi-hoi!)
(Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! ホイホイホーイ)
(Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Hoi-hoi-hoi!)
「全速前進だ〜!」
'Full speed ahead~!'
進め!
Advance!
(進め!)
(Advance!)
太陽はサンサン大航海日和だ
The sun is shining, a perfect day for a voyage
歌え!
Sing!
(歌え!)
(Sing!)
撃
Strike!
あじまる
Ajimaru!
これが星街再演サインぬい
This is the Hoshimachi re-performance signed plush
ローチケ当たったので、解散かも？
Since I won the Lawson ticket, we might dissolve?
声出せ!!
Make some noise!!
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
マリ船長 400万人 おめでとう
Captain Marine, congrats on 4 million!
落選
Rejected
声出して行くぞお！
Let's raise our voices!
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
最高！
The best!
ロボ子さん
Robocosan
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
アキ・ローゼンタール
Aki Rosenthal
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
アーニャ・メルフィッサ
Anya Melfissa
カエラ・コヴァルスキア
Kaela Kovalskia
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
オーロ・クロニー
Ouro Kronii
古石ビジュー
Koseki Bijou
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト
Nerissa Ravencroft
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
Ridin' on Dreams
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉 届け
Harmony, layered words, reach out
Yeah!
言の葉 楽しく 描いては
Drawing words joyfully
ぎこちないと 笑ってた
We laughed, saying it was awkward
未来予想 あの日の続きを 見よう
Let's see the continuation of that day's future prediction
手と手 つないで 明日も 着こなして
Hand in hand, let's wear tomorrow well too
扉を 叩いて 連れて行くよ
I'll knock on the door and take you along
どんなことも きっと 一緒なら 超えて 行ける
Surely we can overcome anything if we're together
La la la la 鳴り止まない 希望の ベル
La la la la, the bell of hope that won't stop ringing
ほら La la la la 聞こえてる？
Look, can you hear it? La la la la
歌
A song
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmony, layered words
鮮やかな 日々の 向こう
Beyond the vivid days
いつも 君と 彩る ストーリー
A story I always color with you
ハーモニー 結んだ 夢が
Harmony, the connected dream
空へ 駆けて 行く
Is galloping toward the sky
煌めきに 乗せて あなたへ
Carrying the sparkle to you
届け メロディー どこまでも
Reach out, melody, wherever you go
Harmony
手を伸ばしたら
When I reach out my hand
足跡に虹がかかる
A rainbow spans across my footprints
君と晴れる
It clears up with you
打ち立てるステージ
The stage we build
Harmony
記した場所へ
To the place we've marked
運ぶ約束を
Carrying the promise
輝きに乗せて
Setting it upon the radiance
世界へ
To the world
響け
Resonate
メロディ
Melody
いつまでも
Forever
君と踏み出したあの一歩 あの瞬間が
That first step I took with you, that moment
宝物だって胸を張る 今
I can proudly say now that it's a treasure
歩いて 話して はしゃいで 笑って行くんだ
Walking, talking, frolicking, and laughing together
色褪せないまま
Without ever fading
混ざり合う僕らの声 ほら
Our voices blending together, look
聞こえてる
Can you hear it?
歌
The song
Harmony
重ねたことが
Everything we've layered
鮮やかな日々の向こう
Beyond the vivid days
ずっと君と
Always with you
彩るストーリー
A story we color
Harmony
結んだ夢が
The dreams we've tied
空へ駆けてゆく
Go racing toward the sky
煌めきに乗せて
Setting them upon the sparkle
あなたへ
To you
世界へ
To the world
響け
Resonate
愛を
With love
込めて
Heartfelt
メロディ
Melody
どこまでも
Everywhere
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ
Clear, clear, clear
輝くんだよ
Shining bright
呼び合う声を
With our voices calling out
合図に
As the signal
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ
Clear, clear, clear
探しに行く
Going to find it
スタートは何度だって
The start is as many times as it takes
光が続くさ
The light will continue
ただ 始まりたかったんだ
We just wanted to begin
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Lit in the distant darkness
それは 眩しすぎた名前
That was a name too bright
それは 優しすぎる祈りで
That was a prayer too kind
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
Stretching out my hand to get closer
甘え合わず 結び合った
Not depending on each other, but tied together
ほら 今 前を向く物語になった
Look, it's become a story of looking forward
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ
Clear, clear, clear
輝くんだよ
Shining bright
悔しさも愛おしさも
Both regret and endearment
連れておいで
Bring them along
馳せ 夢 弾め
Racing dreams, bounce
飛び立てるさ
You can take flight
ささやかな祈り 光
A modest prayer, a light
終わりなき兆し
An endless sign
君を見つけたこと
That I found you
胸を張れるよ
I can be proud of it
どこから どこまで
From where to where
アワライフ 晴れ 晴れ
Our Life, clear, clear
Harmony
頼りない横顔を
A profile not to be relied on
笑おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
Let's laugh, it's nothing to be ashamed of
誰も解けない今を知り
Knowing the present that no one can unravel
いつか また会えを増したい
Someday, I want to meet you again more and more
あの日 ゼロに始まったストーリー
The story that started at zero that day
数えきれない言葉の
The countless words
数えるような想いじゃないさ
Aren't feelings you can count
ほら 今 僕らを一つに呼ぼう
Look, now let's call us as one
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ
Clear, clear, clear
美しいんだよ
It's beautiful
許しあえる切ない
Heartbreakingly forgivable
夜は煌めく
The night sparkles
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ
Clear, clear, clear
瞬く空
The twinkling sky
相応しい日々とは 君と歩くことさ
Appropriate days are walking with you
君と歩む物語なんだ
It's a story I walk with you
「ただいま」を聞けば
If I hear "I'm home"
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
I'll shout "Welcome back"
当たり前じゃないから
Because it's not something to be taken for granted
Parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! We're gonna shine
呼び合う声を合図に
With the voices calling out as our signal
Parade, parade, parade! 暗がりを満たすのは
Parade, parade, parade! Filling the darkness is...
君と僕だ
...you and me
Parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! We're gonna shine
悔しさも愛しさも
Both the frustrations and the affections
連れておいで
Bring them along
Parade, parade, parade! 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade! Going to search
風、夢、羽、飛び乗ってさ
Riding on the wind, dreams, and wings
ささやかな光
A modest light
さぁ、ここからが僕らの
Now, from here starts our...
素敵なスタートさ
...wonderful start
君と 飛び込んでゆく
Diving in with you...
ここから Parade, parade, parade!
...from here, Parade, parade, parade!
セブンスフェス！ ステージ4、スタートです！
7th Fes! Stage 4, starting now!
Watch out!
Warning! Warning! I'm the baddest
ホロライブ、セブンスフェス！
Hololive, 7th Fes!
幕張！ 最後のステージだ！
Makuhari! It's the final stage!
君から見れば 僕は世間
From your perspective, I'm just the world
理不尽な事案黙って過ごす恐怖を待つ
Silently enduring unfair incidents, waiting for fear
光って見れば 露わな貴方に
When viewed with light, to the exposed you
行うと誓った ところでしょうもない
I vowed to carry it out, but it's no use now
変わって変わらぬ 心の中から響く
Resonating from within a heart that changes yet stays the same
嘘たちが違かったと ただ青空を眺めて
Saying the lies were different, just gazing at the blue sky
明日を重ねてゆく
Piling up the tomorrows
思い出してしまうのに
Even though I end up remembering
誤魔化してしまうのは
The reason I keep deceiving myself
確かにあった後悔から
Is because of the regrets that certainly existed
あぁ 違ったんだってさよならさよなら
Ah, saying it was different, goodbye, goodbye
光に触れるたび 濁ってしまうよね
Every time I touch the light, it becomes muddy, doesn't it?
止まってしまうの
It just comes to a stop
震える my body 逃げる瞬間ばかり
My body is trembling, always moments of running away
嘘で染まったような日々じゃ響かないと 君は笑って
Smiling and saying it won't resonate in days stained with lies
また夜明けを待つの 君の中のフレーバー
Waiting for the dawn again, the flavor within you
何もないまま また道を歩いている
Walking the path again with nothing
迷い空を重ねて 解き放した正体
Piling up the lost skies, the identity I've released
誤魔化しきれなかった 心が求める熱を
The heat my heart seeks that I couldn't fully hide
憧れが照らした
Illuminated by longing
明日を重ねてゆく
Piling up the tomorrows
思い出してしまうのに
Even though I end up remembering
誤魔化してしまうのは
The reason I keep deceiving myself
大人になった後悔から
Because of the regrets of having become an adult
あぁ 月明かりの夜はさよならさよなら
Ah, on the moonlit night, goodbye, goodbye
光を繋ぐたび 濁ってしまうよね
Every time I connect the light, it becomes muddy, doesn't it?
歩んでいく道より今を 移ろい焦がしてしまう日々を
More than the path I walk, the days where I drift and yearn for the now
あぁ 私はまだ止まらない
Ah, I won't stop yet
夜空に浮かぶ月の光を 見上げるランウェイ
Running the runway, looking up at the moonlight in the night sky
星の方へ 行こう
Let's go towards the stars
道標にして 帰る場所へ
Making them my signpost to the place I return to
明日を重ねてゆく
Piling up the tomorrows
思い出してしまうのに
Even though I end up remembering
誤魔化してしまうのは
The reason I keep deceiving myself
確かにあった後悔から
Is because of the regrets that certainly existed
あぁ 違ったんだってさよならさよなら
Ah, saying it was different, goodbye, goodbye
光に触れるたび 濁ってしまうよね
Every time I touch the light, it becomes muddy, doesn't it?
ビビデバ・バビデブ・ブーでアイ
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo, you and I
So, what things are on move?
誰の愛を模したって
No matter whose love you imitate,
愛を模したって
even if you imitate love.
皆様ー！
Everyone!
この愚民はお愛しの La+...
This plebeian is the beloved La+...
早く抱きしめて チュッチュッしてさぁ！
Hurry and hug me, give me some kisses!
待っててね、貴様は今から La+ に夢中になっちゃう！
Wait for it, you're about to fall head over heels for La+!
抑えきれないの 私の鼓動がクチュクチュしてる
I can't suppress it, my heart is thumping away
切なな瞳 尖る唇 無邪気な笑顔
Painful eyes, pouting lips, an innocent smile
もう止まらないの 私の中がグズグズしてる
I can't stop now, my inside is feeling all mushy
溢れ出しちゃう 嗚呼 頭の先までビンビン感じちゃう
It's overflowing, ah, I feel it tingling to the tip of my head
美しければいいの この仔猫ちゃん
As long as you're beautiful, my little kitten
隠れてないでよ 顔見せて
Don't hide away, show me your face
風速秒速 100パーセント
Wind speed, velocity 100%
出力最大
Maximum output
見つけた！
Found you!
胸がキュンキュン 愛は止まらないの
My heart is pounding, my love just won't stop
好き好き 大好き marry me
I love you, I love you so much, marry me
私だけのお姫様 もう離さない ずっと
My only princess, I'll never let you go, forever
境界線を引き上げましょう 神様だって困っちゃう
Let's pull up the boundary line, even God will be troubled
思い立ったのでいっちゃおう
Now that I've decided, let's go
ハネムーン・アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Honeymoon Un Deux Trois
お嫁 ハネムーン・アン・ドゥ・トロワ
The bride's honeymoon un deux trois
何してんの？ ダーリン お帰りなさいの チュッ... は！
What are you doing, darling? A welcome home kiss... ha!
さて、ご飯にしようかな？ お風呂にしようかな？
Now, should we have dinner? Or a bath?
それとも... ラ・プラス？
Or maybe... La+?
今日はこれから二人で 楽しいショッピングデート！
Today, we're going on a fun shopping date together!
ダーリン、もう準備できてる？
Darling, are you ready yet?
ダーリン、どこにいるの？
Darling, where are you?
もしからして、 La+ とかくれんぼしたいのかな？
Could it be you want to play hide-and-seek with La+?
テーブルの下、クローゼットの中かな？
Under the table? Inside the closet?
よし、 La+ 本気出しちゃうぞ！
Alright, La+ is going to get serious!
100パーセント！
100 percent!
甘い鼓動のリズム
A rhythm of sweet heartbeats
赤い糸で二人繋がっているの
We're connected by a red thread of fate
ハートがビンビン come on baby
My heart is thumping, come on baby
見つけた！
Found you!
恋はもう 誰にも止められないの
This love can't be stopped by anyone anymore
好き好き 大好き marry me
I love you, I love you so much, marry me
二人だけの愛の巣から もう逃がさない ずっと
From our love nest for two, I'll never let you go, forever
永遠の愛を誓いましょう 神様サインはハレルヤ
Let's swear eternal love, God's sign is Hallelujah
がまんできない 早く行っちゃおう
I can't wait anymore, let's go quickly
ゴー・トゥ・ヘブン
Go to heaven
檻の中に囚われて
Trapped inside a cage
こりゃ いっつ・ま・い・らぶ
This is my love
健やかなるときも 病めるときも 命ある限り
In sickness and in health, as long as we both shall live
ラブラブチュッチュすることを誓いまーす！
I swear to be all lovey-dovey and kissy-kissy!
世界で一番 愛してるよ
I love you more than anyone in the world
ベイビー もう私を一人にしないで
Baby, don't leave me alone anymore
あなたがいないとダメなの
I can't go on without you
寂しがり屋な私の そばにいて ずっと
Stay by my side forever, since I get lonely
皆様ー！ 愛してるよー！
Everyone! I love you!
胸がキュンキュン 愛は止まらないの
My heart is pounding, my love just won't stop
好き好き 大好き marry me
I love you, I love you so much, marry me
私だけのお姫様 もう離さない ずっと
My only princess, I'll never let you go, forever
境界線を引き上げましょう 神様だって困っちゃう
Let's pull up the boundary line, even God will be troubled
思い立ったのでいっちゃおう
Now that I've decided, let's go
ハネムーン・アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Honeymoon Un Deux Trois
お嫁 ハネムーン・アン・ドゥ・トロワ
The bride's honeymoon un deux trois
ありがとう、ダーリン！
Thank you, darling!
チュッ！
Kiss!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
Ah! Marine! 審議拒否! めっちゃ チュッ!
Ah! Marine! Objection! Big kiss!
……めっちゃ好～～～～き
...I really looooove you!
ドクロの旗
Skull flag
Number 1
オンボロパーカー
Raggedy parka
Number 2
リップに眼帯は
Lip and eyepatch are...
Number 3
使用済み
...already used!
How much?
100万！
1 million!
からの？
And then?
1億！
100 million!
からの？
And then?
1兆！
1 trillion!
もっと声！ How much?
Louder! How much?
1000！
1,000!
からの？
And then?
2000！
2,000!
からの？
And then?
3000！
3,000!
ぶっ飛んで
Blown away...
5000兆！
5,000 trillion!
欲しい？欲しい？お前ら
Do you want it? You guys...
マリン助けて欲しいの？
Do you want Marine to save you?
しょうがない
I guess I have to...
参上！ホショマリン
Houshou Marine is here!
バレバレバレ　バレバレパレード
Pare-pare-pare, pare-pare-parade
売り出せや　お宝
Sell it off, the treasure!
ドパドパドパッパッパ
Dopa-dopa-dopa-pa-pa!
コインでも　ちゅきコイン
Even with coins, I love coins
商人降臨
A merchant descends
なんてね
Just kidding!
垂れ流れ　欲望かだされ
Desires flowing out, overflowed
ベラベラポンド　乱され
Bera-bera-pound, disturbed
どきどき　恋ぐるぐる世界が回され
Thump-thump, love spinning the world around
超（でっ）スチャーミングな誘惑ハンパない
Super charming temptation is no joke!
いざ Hammer
Now, the hammer!
Congratulations! Get!
円　ドル　ポンド　ユーロ　マニシュ　シュキシュキ
Yen, Dollar, Pound, Euro, Money-sh, love it!
ルピア　リーラ　ウォン　元　ドン
Rupiah, Lira, Won, Yuan, Dong
How much?
ドロカバー　セットチャー
Doro-cover, set-cha!
レアル　マルク　コロン　シュシュ
Real, Mark, Colon, Shushu
貝殻　小判　金銀銅
Shells, koban, gold, silver, copper
How much?
お宝売って　入金やって
Sell the treasure, make the deposit
お船奪って　Happy Peace!
Capture the ship, Happy Peace!
粛清して　嵐やって
Purge them, make a storm
抜刀、サンキュー
Draw sword, thank you!
難破船で　お宝ピッカー
Picker of treasures from shipwrecks
アドナ効果　ほら打ち勝って
Adona effect, look, overcome it
大発見　これはマリンと命名するのだ
Great discovery! I'll name this 'Marine'!
愛をチェック
Check the love
Number 5
ブランチのフォーク
Brunch fork
Number 6
ヨダレスカーフ
Drool scarf
まだ足りない
Not enough yet
次はセブン
Next is seven
Number 7
サービスサービス
Service, service!
Number 8
名も無きボロきれのギュッたく
A pile of nameless rags!
How much?
1000！
1,000!
からの？
And then?
1億！
100 million!
からの？
And then?
1兆！
1 trillion!
もっと声！ How much?
Louder! How much?
1000！
1,000!
からの？
And then?
2000！
2,000!
からの？
And then?
3000！
3,000!
ぶっ飛んで
Blown away...
5000兆！
5,000 trillion!
ドキドキしてルージュ？
Heart-racing, rouge?
幕張、いきますよ～！
Makuhari, here we go!
ねぇ、言ったよね？
Hey, you said it, right?
年齢なんて関係ないってさ
That age doesn't matter, right?
そういう面倒くさいのも　含めて愛してくれるって
That you'd love me, including that annoying stuff
ねぇねぇ、言ったよね？言ってない？
Hey hey, you said it, right? Did you not?
ふーん、そういうこと言うんだ
Hmph, so that's what you say
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど
By the way, on this ship, 'Beautiful Girl Innocent' applies
流させて
Let me go
魔法で輝く
Shining with magic
秘密の素顔はキミにだけ
My secret face is just for you
特別ですよ？
It's special, you know?
Ah 魅せちゃうよ
Ah, I'll show you
湊（みなと）なんかじゃ　はしゃげないわ
I can't frolic at a port...
近頃はね
...lately, you know
だからあの島にして欲しい気分
So I feel like making it that island
CHU!
勇を出し　響き渡る
Summon courage, let it resound
君の1番狙い撃ちよ
Aiming for your number one spot
そろそろ本当は自信ないけど　頑張っちゃう
About time... I'm not confident, but I'll try!
キュキュキュンキュン
Kyu-kyu-kyun-kyun
恋する気持ち　十分なのだわ
Feelings of love are more than enough
全然なっちゃうわ　オトナの階段
I'll climb the stairs to adulthood completely
ドキドキしてルージュ？
Heart-racing, rouge?
お許しください　このマリンの
Please forgive this Marine's...
魅力　魔力　フトコロ力
...charm, magic power, and pocket power!
罪な女ね
What a sinful woman
離さないで
Don't let go
捕まっていて
Keep holding on
世界の広さ　見せてあげるから
I'll show you how wide the world is
勇を出し　響き渡る
Summon courage, let it resound
君の1番狙い撃ちよ
Aiming for your number one spot
そろそろ冗談も大好きだけど　真剣よ
About time... I love jokes, but I'm serious
キュキュキュンキュン
Kyu-kyu-kyun-kyun
恋する気持ち　十分なのだわ
Feelings of love are more than enough
全然なっちゃうわ　オトナの階段
I'll climb the stairs to adulthood completely
ドキドキしてルージュ？
Heart-racing, rouge?
まだ早い！
Too early!
マリンじゃなくて
I'm not just Marine...
マリン船長だ！
...I'm Captain Marine!
美少女無罪パイレーツ
Bishoujo Muzai Pirates
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
神様の花びらを
The petals of God
ある人は美しくと呟いた
Someone murmured they were beautiful
この地球の横顔は
The profile of this Earth...
どう見えてる？君の世界では
how does it look in your world?
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down,
亡くしそうなものだけ振り落とした
shaking off only the things I'm about to lose.
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to pick them up in my palm,
指の隙間すり抜け消えてった
they slipped through my fingers and disappeared.
形あるものだけが全てじゃないけど
It's not that only things with form are everything, but...
形あるものがどうしても欲しいよ
I still want something with form no matter what.
この世界を
This world...
変えることはきっと出来ないけど
I surely can't change it, but...
君の中の世界なら変えられるはず
in the world inside you, it should be changeable.
芽吹いて咲いて実って晴れて
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, and clearing up,
何一つ欠かせないから
because not a single thing can be missing.
最後に君が笑ってくれれば
If you smile at the end,
もうそれだけでいい
that's enough for me.
言葉の綾を紡ぐ人
Those who spin figures of speech,
優しさを編む人
those who weave kindness,
それぞれの正義を分かち合えたら
if we could share our respective justice...
あらばまた矛盾と辻褄合わせ
Then there's contradictions and consistency again,
そんな刹那を抱え今日を生きる
holding such moments, we live today.
分け合った灯火
The light we shared,
隣から隣へ繋がって一つに
connecting from neighbor to neighbor into one.
夜の帳へ息を吹き込んだ
Breathed life into the veil of night,
君じゃなきゃダメなんだ
it has to be you.
このまま寝てしまうには勿体ないほど
So much that it's a waste to just sleep like this,
優しさに包まった夜だった
it was a night wrapped in kindness.
はっきり浮かび上がった夢の輪郭
The clearly emerging outline of a dream,
それは確かに愛だった
that was certainly love.
月が見守る今夜、一瞬を捕まえて
Tonight watched by the moon, catch the moment,
煌めく星
twinkling stars.
彩りや形、温度や響き
Colors, shapes, temperature, and resonance,
まるで何もかも違う僕らだけど
though we are all completely different,
きっと最後に歩幅で繋がって
surely at the end, we'll connect by our pace.
この世界を
This world...
変えることはきっと出来ないけど
I surely can't change it, but...
君の中の世界なら変えられるはず
in the world inside you, it should be changeable.
芽吹いて咲いて実って晴れて
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, and clearing up,
何一つ欠かせないから
because not a single thing can be missing.
最後に君が笑ってくれれば
If you smile at the end,
もうそれだけでいい
that's enough for me.
みんな聞いてくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for listening!
楽しんでくれましたかー！？
Did you all have fun!?
ステージ4、まだまだ続きます！
Stage 4 is still continuing!
盛り上がっていきましょー！
Let's get fired up!
ただいまー！
We're back!
7th fes ステージ4、始まりましたー！
7th Fes Stage 4 has begun!
EXPOもフェスも最終日だよ！まだまだいけるよねー！？
It's the final day for the EXPO and Fes! You're still with us, right!?
ちょっとね、今歌って踊ったばかりで、疲れてなーい！です！
I just finished singing and dancing, but I'm NOT tired at all!
まだまだ元気もりもりあります！
I'm still full of energy!
すごい元気だね！
You're so energetic!
でもこんなにさ、たくさんの声援を浴びたらさ、パワーもらっちゃうよね！
But when you receive this much cheering, it really gives you power!
本当にさ！でもまだまだステージは続いていきますので、皆さん
Exactly! But the stage is still continuing, everyone...
右肩上がりで、もっとでかい声...
Let's keep ramping up with even louder voices...
すごすぎるよね！
This is just too incredible!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
じゃあちょっと自己紹介からさせていただきます！
Well then, let's start with some introductions!
はい！
All right!
カワイイ・ポジティブ・
Cute, positive,
ジーニアス！
Genius!
めっちゃ嬉しい！ホロライブDEV_IS ReGLOSSの
I'm so happy! From hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS,
一条莉々華だよ！こんにりりー！
it's Ichijou Ririka! Kon-niriri!
こんにりりー！
Kon-niriri!
めっちゃ嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
そして！
And next!
はい！DEV_IS hololive DEV_IS所属ReGLOSSの儒烏風亭らでんでーす！
Yes! From hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS, it's Juufuutei Raden!
なになになに？
Wait, what was that?
ええ！？
Ehh!?
さっきまでさ、あんなにさ、
A second ago you were like,
「ちょっとドキドキする〜」とか言ってたのに！
"I'm getting a bit nervous!"
絶好調じゃん！
But you're in top form!
皆さん、楽しんでますかー！？
Everyone, are you having a good time!?
イェーイ！
Yeah!
うわぁ、ペンライトもリリらでの色にしてくれてる！
Wow, the penlights are all in Riri-Raden colors!
ねー、すごい！ありがとう！
Right? Amazing! Thank you!
はい！ということで、
Right! So anyway,
え、もうすでに何曲か、みんなにね、お披露目できたと思うんですけれども、
we've already performed several songs for you today,
はい！
Yes!
今回ちょっとね、7thフェスのテーマ、
this time, as the theme for the 7th Fes,
「Ride on Dreams」ということで、
"Ride on Dreams,"
ステージと、そして皆さんの、お客さんのね、架け橋の形が、
the bridge between the stage and all of you, the audience,
トロッコとして、ね、出てきました！
took the form of carts (torokko)!
すごかったよー！
It was incredible!
実際にね、私たちも乗らせてもらったんですけど、
We actually got to ride on them ourselves,
もう本当にみんなの笑顔が、嬉しそうな顔が見えました！
and we could see everyone's smiles and happy faces so clearly!
見えてたよー！もうめっちゃ見えてたよ、顔とか持ってるグッズとか！
We saw you! We could see your faces and the merch you were holding!
最高！
The best!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
もうね、なんかせっかくMC務めさせていただいたから、
Since we've been given this chance to do the MC,
なんかやりたいことあるんじゃないの？
isn't there something you want to do?
あれ！？
Wait, what!?
社長、何やりたい？
President, what do you want to do?
いやもう、一番最初の全体曲の時から、
Well, ever since the very first group song,
みんなのね、こう掛け声とか、ペンライトとかが、
everyone's cheers and penlights,
もう、ぶわああああ！って、
they were just like, WHOOSH!
ぶわああああって嬉しいくらい来てて、
Coming at us so fast it made me so happy,
ちょっとそれをこのMC中にもちょっとやりたいんですけど、いいですか！？
so I'd like to do a bit of that during the MC too, is that okay!?
いいですかー！？
Is it okay!?
やったー！
Yay!
じゃあ莉々華はペンライトを使って、ちょっとみんなと、
Then, Ririka wants to use the penlights,
交流したいです！いいですか皆さん！ペンライトの準備は！
to interact with everyone! Are you ready with your penlights!?
社長の色は分かりやすいもんね！
The President's color is easy to spot!
じゃあ、ちょっと全部を、
Okay, let's try having everything,
濃いピンク！薄いピンクじゃないですよ！
Deep pink! Not light pink!
莉々華の濃いピンクにしてみて、もらってもいいですか！？
Could you all turn them to Ririka's deep pink!?
もうできてるよ！
It's already done!
うわああああ！すごい！
Wooooah! Amazing!
よかったねー！お花畑みたい！
That's great! It looks like a flower garden!
じゃあ次は、らでんのカラーである、黄色にしてもらってもいいですか！？
Next, could you change them to Raden's color, yellow!?
らでん色もしてくれるの！？
You'll do Raden's color too!?
うわあああ！ありがとう！
Waaaaah! Thank you!
ありがとう！最高！
Thank you! The best!
じゃあ次は、莉々華が「ピンク」って言ったらピンク、「黄色」って言ったら黄色にしてね！
Okay, when Ririka says "pink," turn it pink; when I say "yellow," turn it yellow!
できるかな！？
Can you do it!?
嘘でしょ！？そんなのできる！？
No way!? Can they really do that!?
あ！ピンクになってるよ！
Oh! It's turning pink!
うわあああ！すごい！
Waaaaah! Amazing!
あ、どんどん変わってる！どんどん変わってる！
Oh, it's changing! It's changing bit by bit!
カチカチカチ変わってる！
Click-click-click, it's changing!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
じゃあ、好きな色！
Now, your favorite color!
ねー、すごい、お花畑みたい！
Wow, incredible, it really is like a flower garden!
ありがとうございます、とっても嬉しいです！
Thank you so much, I'm very happy!
じゃあらでんは何やりたい？
So Raden, what do you want to do?
え、らでんはもう分かってると思うけど、
Well, I think everyone already knows, but...
らでんがちょっとこのDAY3のMCとして出たということは、
the fact that I'm here as the MC for Day 3 means...
今日は何曜日だっけかな〜？
I wonder what day of the week it is today?
みんな知ってるよね！？らでんが「明日は？」って言ったら、
Everyone knows, right!? When I say "Tomorrow is?"...
皆さんも生まれてきて一番のデカい声で、
I want you all to shout with the loudest voice of your life,
「月曜日！」って叫んでくださいね、いいですか！？
"Monday!" Okay!?
いいよー！
Ready!
月曜日ですよ！行きますよ！
It's Monday! Here we go!
明日はー！？
Tomorrow is!?
月曜日ー！
Monday!
最高！ありがとう！
Perfect! Thank you!
いやでも、明日が月曜日でも、
But even if tomorrow is Monday,
そんな疲れ、吹っ飛ぶくらい今日は最高のパフォーマンスを、
we're going to give you such a great performance today that all that fatigue will blow away!
みんなで届けていきますので、
We'll be delivering it together,
皆さん、まだまだ盛り上がっていきますよー！
so everyone, let's keep this excitement going!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いいね！
Nice!
もっといけるよね！
We can go harder, right?!
まだまだいけるよね！
We can still go harder, right?!
最高！
Awesome!
はい、ということで、あのね、今回現地に来てくださってるみんなと
Alright, so, you know, to everyone here at the venue...
配信で見てくださっているみんなも
and everyone watching the stream too!
そう、コメントも見えてますからね！
Yeah, we can see your comments!
見えてありますので、えー、配信のみんなはハッシュタグ
We can see them, so for those on the stream, please use the hashtag...
＃ホロライブフェスエキスポ24Day3 でたくさんポストしてくれたら嬉しいです！
#hololivefesEXPO24Day3 and post a lot, we'd be so happy!
嬉しいね！
That would be great!
そしてそして、楽しいお知らせがあるんですけど
And also, and also, we have some fun news!
楽しいお知らせ、何ー？！
Fun news? What is it?!
YouTubeとTikTokでご覧の方はここまでー！
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, this is the end!
どうしよう！
What should we do?!
はい、でもね、よかったら皆さんまだまだ
Yes, but, if you'd like, everyone...
楽しいライブは続きますので、引き続き見てもらえると嬉しいです！
the fun live show continues, so we hope you'll keep watching!
いっぱい声出して応援してね！
Shout out loud and cheer for us!
応援してください！
Please cheer for us!
それではですね、ちょっと次の曲に入りたいと思いますので
Now then, we're about to move on to the next song...
「せーの」って言ったら、みんなで今回のね、テーマである「Ridin’ on Dreams」と叫んでもらえたら嬉しいです。いいですか？
so when I say 'Ready, go!', I'd love for everyone to shout this event's theme, 'Ridin' on Dreams'. Are you ready?
いいですかー？！
Are you ready?!
OK!
それじゃあいくよ！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, go!
Ridin’ on Dreams!
Ridin' on Dreams!
引き続き楽しんでってね！
Keep having fun!
Ridin' on Dreams
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free part of the show has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!